<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About the Package
================================
An action pack for ARA that leverages the CA RA inbound REST API. This way, the two products can trigger and get status between each other, enabling the construct of a master-slave configuration

=Supported versions=

=Setup=
* The Agent should be able to access CA RA rest api endpoint URL in order to make HTTP requests.

=Common Inputs=
(None)

=Actions=
Following actions are supported.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.GET_APPLICATIONS
* Action Description:  This action lists all the applications which are present inside CA RA server.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.GET_ENVIRONMENTS
* Action Description:  This action lists all the Environments present for an application in  CA RA server.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_RELEASE
* Action Description:   This action deletes a release using basic release parameters.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.LOAD_MANIFEST
* Action Description:   This action loads a manifest file to a deployment plan.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.GET_APPLICATION_BY_ID
* Action Description:  This action retrieves a specific application by entering the application id.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.GET_ENVIRONMENT_BY_ID
* Action Description:   This action retrieves specific environment details using the application id and the environment id.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_ARTIFACT_VERSION
* Action Description:   This action Deletes an artifact-version.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_ARTIFACT_PACKAGE
* Action Description:   This action creates an empty artifact package.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_PROJECT
* Action Description:   This action creates a new project for a specified application.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.STOP_DEPLOYMENT
* Action Description:  This action stops a running deployment.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.RUN_DEPLOYMENTS
* Action Description:  This action creates a deployment from an existing deployment plan.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_DEPLOYMENT_PLAN
* Action Description: Create Deployment Plan.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.GET_DEPLOYMENT_STATUS
* Action Description: Gets the state of the deployment.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.LOAD_TOKENS
* Action Description: Loads token values to an environment.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.CREATE_TEMPLATE_PROPERTY
* Action Description: Create template property for a given application and category id.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.UPDATE_TEMPLATE_PROPERTY
* Action Description: Update template property for a given application and category id.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.DELETE_TEMPLATE_PROPERTY
* Action Description: Delete template property for a given application and category id.

* Action name:  PCK.AUTOMIC_CA_RA.PUB.ACTION.RUN_DEPLOYMENT_PLAN
* Action Description: Creates a deployment plan from an existing deployment template.]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>